const randomQuestions = [
  {
    question: "What is the capital of France?",
    options: ["Paris", "London", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
    correctAnswer: 0, //"Paris",
    id: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What does Porphyrophile stands for?",
    options: [
      "Confidence",
      "Love for color purple",
      "Fear of color purple",
      "Love for colors",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1, //"Love for color purple",
    id: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which country defeated the Italians in the 'Adwa war'?",
    options: ["Belgium", "Malta", "Ethiopia", "Egpyt"],
    correctAnswer: 2, //"Ethiopia",
    id: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "The Kikuyu people can be found in which country?",
    options: ["Madagascar", "Uganda", "Kenya", "Chad"],
    correctAnswer: 2, //"Kenya",
    id: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Okun subgroup refers to group of Yoruba people that can be found in ______ state.",
    options: ["Edo", "Kwara", "Benue", "Kogi"],
    correctAnswer: 3, //"Kogi",
    id: 5,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The monarchical system the Yoruba's practices is a constitutional monarchy.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: 0, //"True",
    id: 6,
  },
  {
    question: "______ is the last country to gain independence in Africa.",
    options: ["Sao Tome and Principe", "Djibouti", "South-Sudan", "Angola"],
    correctAnswer: 2, //"South Sudan",
    id: 7,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Sayfawa dynasty of the Kanem-Bornu ruled for more than ______ years",
    options: ["700", "800", "920", "1730"],
    correctAnswer: 1, //"800",
    id: 8,
  },
  {
    question: "World War I started _____ and ended ______.",
    options: ["1914, 1918", "1939, 1945", "1915,1920", "1814,1818"],
    correctAnswer: 0, //"1914,1918",
    id: 9,
  },
  {
    question: "The cold war was after _____.",
    options: ["American Revolution", "WWI", "Chinese Revolution", "WWII"],
    correctAnswer: 1, //"WWI",
    id: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "Bolivia can be found in _____.",
    options: ["Asia", "Africa", "S/America", "N/America"],
    correctAnswer: 2, //"S/America",
    id: 11,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Nogales Senora and Nogales Arizona can be found in ______ and ______.",
    options: ["Chile,Brazil", "Canada,US", "Columbia,US", "Mexico, US"],
    correctAnswer: 3, //"Mexico, US",
    id: 12,
  },
  {
    question: "The Ottoman empire is peculiar to present day ______.",
    options: ["Algeria", "Egpyt", "Turkey", "Syria"],
    correctAnswer: 2, //"Turkey",
    id: 13,
  },
  {
    question: "____ and ____ are countries in West Africa",
    options: [
      "Zimbabwe and Ghana",
      "Sudan and Uganda",
      "Sudan and South-Sudan",
      "Liberia and Guinea-Bissau",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3, //"Liberia and Guinea-Bissau",
    id: 14,
  },
  {
    question: "All these countries are North Africa countries except _____",
    options: ["Algeria", "Mali", "Egpyt", "Morrocco"],
    correctAnswer: 1, //"Mali",
    id: 15,
  },
  {
    question: "____ is the capital of Sierra-Leone?",
    options: ["Timbuktu", "London", "Freetown", "Lagos"],
    correctAnswer: 2, //"Freetown",
    id: 16,
  },
  {
    question: "Jerusalem is situated where?",
    options: ["Jordan", "Palestine", "Isreal", "US"],
    correctAnswer: 2, //"Isreal",
    id: 17,
  },
  {
    question: "OPEC stands for _______",
    options: [
      "Organization of People Exporting Charcoal",
      "Organization of Petroleum Exporting Country",
      "Oraganization of People Exchanging Cash",
      "Operation Everybody must Co-exist",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1, //"Organization of Petroleum Exporting Country",
    id: 18,
  },
  {
    question: "The Red Indians are natives of present day ______.",
    options: ["Canada", "Britain", "India", "US"],
    correctAnswer: 3, //"US",
    id: 19,
  },
  {
    question: "Söğüt can be found in ______",
    options: ["Jordan", "Syria", "Turkey", "US"],
    correctAnswer: 2, //"Turkey",
    id: 20,
  },
  {
    question:
      "The last independent country in Africa gained her Independce on 9 July 2011.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: 0, //"True",
    id: 21,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Cape Verde/ Cabo Verde gained her independence from Portugal on _______.",
    options: [
      "5th July 1976",
      "5th July 1978",
      "5th July 1975",
      "28th November 1980",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2, //"5th July 1975", island of Hispaniola (the island that makes up modern-day Haiti and the Dominican Republic)
    id: 22,
  },
  {
    question: "The Hispaniola Island makes up modern-day ______ and _______.",
    options: [
      "Haiti and Dominican Republic",
      "Peru and Chile",
      "Bolivia and Argentina",
      "Costa Rica and Gautemala",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0, //"Haiti and Dominican Republic"
    id: 23,
  },
];

export default randomQuestions;
